so I do like most conveniens you a lot
of traveling we all talk about that I
was up in Wisconsin
not long ago I'm not here to brag but
yeah it's exactly right and so people
get super excited about that and I was
up there to see my uncle that was on a
dairy farm in Wisconsin on how it gets
away with it but since resilience snafu
and he I get this is actually true it's
gonna kind of sad but he I got there and
he's all bummed out cuz his dog it just
got ran over by the milk truck and so
that I know so exactly some of you felt
bad some of you laughed because you're
similar to me because it sounds like a
joke I mean I didn't find that out there
wasn't till later but at the time I
thought it was a joke because it has the
rhythm of a joke dog milk or like a song
you might sing during the holidays or
something but so I just went with it I'm
like yeah that's a good one that's funny
we won the chance that happening like 2%
and I you know I I know now I know he
was not pleased he was not pleased turns
out that's not not cool he was very
upset by that but we
we worked it out we had a great time we
went over to the farmers tanning booth
had a blast and we just stuck in our
arms a little while it was great and for
my FFA people head so if you're wearing
blue corduroy tonight blue corduroy it's
so Rocketship's
I just love it it's just it's like it
goes with everything subscribe to drive
our comedy for even more of the world's
largest collection of clean comedy